<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HitoQuotes</string>
    //inspiring
        <string name="quote1">"The best way to predict the future is to create it." - Peter Drucker</string>
        <string name="quote2">"The only way to do great work is to love what you do." - Steve Jobs</string>
        <string name="quote3">"Success is not the key to happiness. Happiness is the key to success. If you love what you are doing, you will be successful." - Albert Schweitzer</string>
        <string name="quote4">"Don’t watch the clock; do what it does. Keep going." - Sam Levenson</string>
        <string name="quote5">"The harder the conflict, the greater the triumph." - George Washington</string>
        <string name="quote6">"The future belongs to those who believe in the beauty of their dreams." - Eleanor Roosevelt</string>
        <string name="quote7">"It does not matter how slowly you go as long as you do not stop." - Confucius</string>
        <string name="quote8">"Start where you are. Use what you have. Do what you can." - Arthur Ashe</string>
        <string name="quote9">"Believe you can and you're halfway there." - Theodore Roosevelt</string>
        <string name="quote10">"Your time is limited, don’t waste it living someone else’s life." - Steve Jobs</string>
        <string name="quote11">"The only limit to our realization of tomorrow is our doubts of today." - Franklin D. Roosevelt</string>
        <string name="quote12">"Don't be afraid to give up the good to go for the great." - John D. Rockefeller</string>
        <string name="quote13">"I find that the harder I work, the more luck I seem to have." - Thomas Jefferson</string>
        <string name="quote14">"Success usually comes to those who are too busy to be looking for it." - Henry David Thoreau</string>
        <string name="quote15">"Success is not final, failure is not fatal: It is the courage to continue that counts." - Winston Churchill</string>
        <string name="quote16">"You miss 100% of the shots you don’t take." - Wayne Gretzky</string>
        <string name="quote17">"Act as if what you do makes a difference. It does." - William James</string>
        <string name="quote18">"What lies behind us and what lies before us are tiny matters compared to what lies within us." - Ralph Waldo Emerson</string>
        <string name="quote19">"Keep your face always toward the sunshine—and shadows will fall behind you." - Walt Whitman</string>
        <string name="quote20">"The best revenge is massive success." - Frank Sinatra</string>
        <string name="quote21">"Dream big and dare to fail." - Norman Vaughan</string>
        <string name="quote22">"The only way to achieve the impossible is to believe it is possible." - Charles Kingsleigh</string>
        <string name="quote23">"Life is 10% what happens to us and 90% how we react to it." - Charles R. Swindoll</string>
        <string name="quote24">"The purpose of our lives is to be happy." - Dalai Lama</string>
        <string name="quote25">"You are never too old to set another goal or to dream a new dream." - C.S. Lewis</string>
        <string name="quote26">"To succeed in life, you need two things: ignorance and confidence." - Mark Twain</string>
        <string name="quote27">"In order to succeed, your desire for success should be greater than your fear of failure." - Bill Cosby</string>
        <string name="quote28">"It always seems impossible until it’s done." - Nelson Mandela</string>
        <string name="quote29">"The only person you are destined to become is the person you decide to be." - Ralph Waldo Emerson</string>
        <string name="quote30">"Don't judge each day by the harvest you reap but by the seeds that you plant." - Robert Louis Stevenson</string>
        <string name="quote31">"The journey of a thousand miles begins with one step." - Lao Tzu</string>
        <string name="quote32">"What you get by achieving your goals is not as important as what you become by achieving your goals." - Zig Ziglar</string>
        <string name="quote33">"The way to get started is to quit talking and begin doing." - Walt Disney</string>
        <string name="quote34">"I have not failed. I've just found 10,000 ways that won't work." - Thomas A. Edison</string>
        <string name="quote35">"Don’t be pushed around by the fears in your mind. Be led by the dreams in your heart." - Roy T. Bennett</string>
        <string name="quote36">"Failure is the condiment that gives success its flavor." - Truman Capote</string>
        <string name="quote37">"The only place where success comes before work is in the dictionary." - Vidal Sassoon</string>
        <string name="quote38">"Opportunities don't happen. You create them." - Chris Grosser</string>
        <string name="quote39">"Good things come to people who wait, but better things come to those who go out and get them." - Anonymous</string>
        <string name="quote40">"If you want to achieve greatness stop asking for permission." - Anonymous</string>
        //Life quotes
        <string name="quote_1">"The purpose of life is not to be happy. It is to be useful, to be honorable, to be compassionate, to have it make some difference that you have lived and lived well." - Ralph Waldo Emerson</string>
        <string name="quote_2">"Life is what happens when you're busy making other plans." - John Lennon</string>
        <string name="quote_3">"In three words I can sum up everything I've learned about life: it goes on." - Robert Frost</string>
        <string name="quote_4">"To live is the rarest thing in the world. Most people exist, that is all." - Oscar Wilde</string>
        <string name="quote_5">"Good friends, good books, and a sleepy conscience: this is the ideal life." - Mark Twain</string>
        <string name="quote_6">"Life is really simple, but we insist on making it complicated." - Confucius</string>
        <string name="quote_7">"Do not take life too seriously. You will never get out of it alive." - Elbert Hubbard</string>
        <string name="quote_8">"Life is a journey that must be traveled no matter how bad the roads and accommodations." - Oliver Goldsmith</string>
        <string name="quote_9">"The greatest pleasure of life is love." - Euripides</string>
        <string name="quote_10">"Life isn't about finding yourself. Life is about creating yourself." - George Bernard Shaw</string>
        <string name="quote_11">"Life is short, and it is up to you to make it sweet." - Sarah Louise Delany</string>
        <string name="quote_12">"Keep smiling, because life is a beautiful thing and there's so much to smile about." - Marilyn Monroe</string>
        <string name="quote_13">"The longer I live, the more I realize the impact of attitude on life." - Charles R. Swindoll</string>
        <string name="quote_14">"Life is ten percent what happens to us and ninety percent how we respond to it." - Charles R. Swindoll</string>
        <string name="quote_15">"The best way to predict your future is to create it." - Peter Drucker</string>
        <string name="quote_16">"Life is a daring adventure or nothing at all." - Helen Keller</string>
        <string name="quote_17">"Life is made of ever so many partings welded together." - Charles Dickens</string>
        <string name="quote_18">"Life isn't about waiting for the storm to pass, it's about learning how to dance in the rain." - Vivian Greene</string>
        <string name="quote_19">"Your time is limited, so don't waste it living someone else's life." - Steve Jobs</string>
        <string name="quote_20">"The big lesson in life, baby, is never be scared of anyone or anything." - Frank Sinatra</string>
        <string name="quote_21">"You only live once, but if you do it right, once is enough." - Mae West</string>
        <string name="quote_22">"In the end, it's not the years in your life that count. It's the life in your years." - Abraham Lincoln</string>
        <string name="quote_23">"The unexamined life is not worth living." - Socrates</string>
        <string name="quote_24">"Life is what we make it, always has been, always will be." - Grandma Moses</string>
        <string name="quote_25">"Life is short, and truth works far and lives long: let us then speak the truth." - Arthur Schopenhauer</string>
        <string name="quote_26">"Live in the sunshine, swim the sea, drink the wild air." - Ralph Waldo Emerson</string>
        <string name="quote_27">"Life is either a great adventure or nothing." - Helen Keller</string>
        <string name="quote_28">"The more you praise and celebrate your life, the more there is in life to celebrate." - Oprah Winfrey</string>
        <string name="quote_29">"Life is a succession of lessons which must be lived to be understood." - Ralph Waldo Emerson</string>
        <string name="quote_30">"The most important thing is to enjoy your life—to be happy—it's all that matters." - Audrey Hepburn</string>
        <string name="quote_31">"Our prime purpose in this life is to help others. And if you can't help them, at least don't hurt them." - Dalai Lama</string>
        <string name="quote_32">"Life is a flower of which love is the honey." - Victor Hugo</string>
        <string name="quote_33">"Life shrinks or expands in proportion to one's courage." - Anais Nin</string>
        <string name="quote_34">"The true secret of happiness lies in taking a genuine interest in all the details of daily life." - William Morris</string>
        <string name="quote_35">"The biggest adventure you can take is to live the life of your dreams." - Oprah Winfrey</string>
        <string name="quote_36">"The good life is one inspired by love and guided by knowledge." - Bertrand Russell</string>
        <string name="quote_37">"The more you know yourself, the more clarity there is. Self-knowledge has no end—you don't come to an achievement, you don't come to a conclusion. It is an endless river." - Jiddu Krishnamurti</string>
        <string name="quote_38">"Life can only be understood backwards; but it must be lived forwards." - Søren Kierkegaard</string>
        <string name="quote_39">"Life is a series of natural and spontaneous changes. Don't resist them—that only creates sorrow. Let reality be reality. Let things flow naturally forward in whatever way they like." - Lao Tzu</string>
        <string name="quote_40">"Dost thou love life? Then do not squander time, for that is the stuff life is made of." - Benjamin Franklin</string>
    //Happiness quotes
        <string name="happiness_quote_1">"Happiness is not something ready made. It comes from your own actions." - Dalai Lama</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_2">"The purpose of our lives is to be happy." - Dalai Lama</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_3">"Happiness is when what you think, what you say, and what you do are in harmony." - Mahatma Gandhi</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_4">"The only joy in the world is to begin." - Cesare Pavese</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_5">"Happiness depends upon ourselves." - Aristotle</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_6">"The most important thing is to enjoy your life—to be happy—it's all that matters." - Audrey Hepburn</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_7">"Happiness is not something you postpone for the future; it is something you design for the present." - Jim Rohn</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_8">"For every minute you are angry you lose sixty seconds of happiness." - Ralph Waldo Emerson</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_9">"Happiness is a warm puppy." - Charles M. Schulz</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_10">"Happiness can exist only in acceptance." - George Orwell</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_11">"Happiness is not in the mere possession of money; it lies in the joy of achievement, in the thrill of creative effort." - Franklin D. Roosevelt</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_12">"Happiness is a state of mind. It's just according to the way you look at things." - Walt Disney</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_13">"Happiness is the art of never holding in your mind the memory of any unpleasant thing that has passed." - Unknown</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_14">"The secret of happiness is not in doing what one likes, but in liking what one does." - James M. Barrie</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_15">"The greatest happiness you can have is knowing that you do not necessarily require happiness." - William Saroyan</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_16">"Happiness is not having what you want. It is appreciating what you have." - Unknown</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_17">"Most folks are as happy as they make up their minds to be." - Abraham Lincoln</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_18">"Happiness is the best makeup." - Drew Barrymore</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_19">"Happiness is the meaning and the purpose of life, the whole aim and end of human existence." - Aristotle</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_20">"Happiness is not a goal; it is a by-product." - Eleanor Roosevelt</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_21">"The only way to find true happiness is to risk being completely cut open." - Chuck Palahniuk</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_22">"Happiness is not something to be pursued; it is a state of being." - Unknown</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_23">"Happiness is a direction, not a place." - Sydney J. Harris</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_24">"The true secret of happiness lies in taking a genuine interest in all the details of daily life." - William Morris</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_25">"Happiness is a choice that requires effort at times." - Aeschylus</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_26">"Happiness is not a matter of events; it depends upon the tides of the mind." - Alice Meynell</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_27">"Happiness is the natural flower of duty." - Phillips Brooks</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_28">"Happiness consists more in conveniences of pleasure that occur every day than in great pieces of good fortune that happen but seldom." - Benjamin Franklin</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_29">"Happiness is a well-balanced combination of love, labour, and luck." - Mary Wilson Little</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_30">"Happiness grows at our own firesides, and is not to be picked in strangers' gardens." - Douglas William Jerrold</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_31">"Happiness is a by-product of an effort to make someone else happy." - Gretta Brooker Palmer</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_32">"Happiness is a way station between too much and too little." - Channing Pollock</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_33">"Happiness is like a kiss. You must share it to enjoy it." - Bernard Meltzer</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_34">"Happiness held is the seed; Happiness shared is the flower." - John Harrigan</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_35">"Happiness is found in doing, not merely possessing." - Napoleon Hill</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_36">"Happiness is having a large, loving, caring, close-knit family in another city." - George Burns</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_37">"Happiness is not having what you want, but wanting what you have." - Rabbi Hyman Schachtel</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_38">"Happiness is when what you think, what you say, and what you do are in harmony." - Mahatma Gandhi</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_39">"Happiness radiates like the fragrance from a flower and draws all good things towards you." - Maharishi Mahesh Yogi</string>
        <string name="happiness_quote_40">"Happiness resides not in possessions, and not in gold, happiness dwells in the soul." - Democritus</string>
    //Wisdom

        <!-- Wisdom Quotes -->
        <string name="wisdom_quote1">"The only true wisdom is in knowing you know nothing." - Socrates</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote2">"Knowing yourself is the beginning of all wisdom." - Aristotle</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote3">"Patience is the companion of wisdom." - Saint Augustine</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote4">"Turn your wounds into wisdom." - Oprah Winfrey</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote5">"The art of being wise is knowing what to overlook." - William James</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote6">"Wisdom is the reward you get for a lifetime of listening when you'd have preferred to talk." - Doug Larson</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote7">"The man of wisdom is never of two minds; the man of benevolence never worries; the man of courage is never afraid." - Confucius</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote8">"Honesty is the first chapter in the book of wisdom." - Thomas Jefferson</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote9">"A loving heart is the truest wisdom." - Charles Dickens</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote10">"The only wisdom we can hope to acquire is the wisdom of humility." - T.S. Eliot</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote11">"Silence is the sleep that nourishes wisdom." - Francis Bacon</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote12">"True wisdom comes to each of us when we realize how little we understand about life, ourselves, and the world around us." - Socrates</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote13">"Knowledge comes, but wisdom lingers." - Alfred Lord Tennyson</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote14">"The invariable mark of wisdom is to see the miraculous in the common." - Ralph Waldo Emerson</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote15">"The road to wisdom? Well, it's plain and simple to express: Err and err and err again but less and less and less." - Piet Hein</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote16">"Wisdom is not a product of schooling but of the lifelong attempt to acquire it." - Albert Einstein</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote17">"A fool thinks himself to be wise, but a wise man knows himself to be a fool." - William Shakespeare</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote18">"It is better to remain silent at the risk of being thought a fool, than to talk and remove all doubt of it." - Maurice Switzer</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote19">"A wise man gets more use from his enemies than a fool from his friends." - Baltasar Gracian</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote20">"Wisdom begins in wonder." - Socrates</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote21">"The wise understand by themselves; fools follow the reports of others." - Tibetan Proverb</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote22">"The seat of knowledge is in the head, of wisdom, in the heart." - William Hazlitt</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote23">"Wisdom is knowing what to do next; skill is knowing how to do it, and virtue is doing it." - David Starr Jordan</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote24">"The beginning of wisdom is to desire it." - Solomon Ibn Gabirol</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote25">"Wisdom is not wisdom when it is derived from books alone." - Horace</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote26">"The only true wisdom is in knowing you know nothing." - Socrates</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote27">"The man who asks a question is a fool for a minute, the man who does not ask is a fool for life." - Confucius</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote28">"Common sense is genius dressed in its working clothes." - Ralph Waldo Emerson</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote29">"By three methods we may learn wisdom: First, by reflection, which is noblest; Second, by imitation, which is easiest; and third by experience, which is the bitterest." - Confucius</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote30">"Wisdom is the daughter of experience." - Leonardo da Vinci</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote31">"To conquer fear is the beginning of wisdom." - Bertrand Russell</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote32">"The wise are instructed by reason; ordinary minds by experience; the stupid, by necessity; and brutes by instinct." - Marcus Tullius Cicero</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote33">"It is the province of knowledge to speak and it is the privilege of wisdom to listen." - Oliver Wendell Holmes Sr.</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote34">"Wisdom is not a product of schooling but of the lifelong attempt to acquire it." - Albert Einstein</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote35">"A single conversation with a wise person is worth a month's study of books." - Chinese Proverb</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote36">"The truest wisdom is a resolute determination." - Napoleon Bonaparte</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote37">"Wisdom is the supreme part of happiness." - Sophocles</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote38">"Wisdom is oftentimes nearer when we stoop than when we soar." - William Wordsworth</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote39">"The art of being wise is knowing what to overlook." - William James</string>
        <string name="wisdom_quote40">"The more wisdom you attain and the more conscious you become, the crazier you will appear to others." - Rza</string>
// Perseverance
        <string name="perseverance_quote1">"Success is not final, failure is not fatal: It is the courage to continue that counts." – Winston Churchill</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote2">"It does not matter how slowly you go as long as you do not stop." – Confucius</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote3">"Perseverance is not a long race; it is many short races one after the other." – Walter Elliot</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote4">"Success seems to be largely a matter of hanging on after others have let go." – William Feather</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote5">"The difference between a successful person and others is not a lack of strength, not a lack of knowledge, but rather a lack of will." – Vince Lombardi</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote6">"I am not judged by the number of times I fail, but by the number of times I succeed: and the number of times I succeed is in direct proportion to the number of times I fail and keep trying." – Tom Hopkins</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote7">"Perseverance is failing 19 times and succeeding the 20th." – Julie Andrews</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote8">"Success is stumbling from failure to failure with no loss of enthusiasm." – Winston Churchill</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote9">"Perseverance, secret of all triumphs." – Victor Hugo</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote10">"Through perseverance many people win success out of what seemed destined to be certain failure." – Benjamin Disraeli</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote11">"It does not matter how many times you get knocked down, but how many times you get up." – Vince Lombardi</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote12">"The only guarantee for failure is to stop trying." – John C. Maxwell</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote13">"Success is not the absence of failure; it's the persistence through failure." – Aisha Tyler</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote14">"Success is no accident. It is hard work, perseverance, learning, studying, sacrifice and most of all, love of what you are doing or learning to do." – Pelé</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote15">"Perseverance is not a long race; it is many short races one after the other." – Walter Elliot</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote16">"It always seems impossible until it's done." – Nelson Mandela</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote17">"I do not think that there is any other quality so essential to success of any kind as the quality of perseverance. It overcomes almost everything, even nature." – John D. Rockefeller</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote18">"The difference between the impossible and the possible lies in a person's determination." – Tommy Lasorda</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote19">"Perseverance is not a passive submission to circumstances—it is a strong and active response to the difficult events of life." – Elizabeth George</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote20">"Perseverance is the hard work you do after you get tired of doing the hard work you already did." – Newt Gingrich</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote21">"Perseverance is the stubborn refusal to quit." – Unknown</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote22">"Many of life's failures are people who did not realize how close they were to success when they gave up." – Thomas Edison</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote23">"Continuous effort—not strength or intelligence—is the key to unlocking our potential." – Winston Churchill</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote24">"It's not that I'm so smart, it's just that I stay with problems longer." – Albert Einstein</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote25">"Perseverance is a great element of success. If you only knock long enough and loud enough at the gate, you are sure to wake up somebody." – Henry Wadsworth Longfellow</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote26">"It does not matter how slowly you go as long as you do not stop." – Confucius</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote27">"The only way to achieve the impossible is to believe it is possible." – Charles Kingsleigh</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote28">"Perseverance is failing 19 times and succeeding the 20th." – Julie Andrews</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote29">"Success seems to be largely a matter of hanging on after others have let go." – William Feather</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote30">"Perseverance, secret of all triumphs." – Victor Hugo</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote31">"Success is not the absence of failure; it's the persistence through failure." – Aisha Tyler</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote32">"Through perseverance many people win success out of what seemed destined to be certain failure." – Benjamin Disraeli</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote33">"Success is not final, failure is not fatal: It is the courage to continue that counts." – Winston Churchill</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote34">"It does not matter how many times you get knocked down, but how many times you get up." – Vince Lombardi</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote35">"Perseverance is not a long race; it is many short races one after the other." – Walter Elliot</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote36">"It does not matter how slowly you go as long as you do not stop." – Confucius</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote37">"Success is no accident. It is hard work, perseverance, learning, studying, sacrifice and most of all, love of what you are doing or learning to do." – Pelé</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote38">"Perseverance is not a long race; it is many short races one after the other." – Walter Elliot</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote39">"The only guarantee for failure is to stop trying." – John C. Maxwell</string>
        <string name="perseverance_quote40">"The difference between the impossible and the possible lies in a person's determination." – Tommy Lasorda</string>
    //change
        <string name="change_quote1">"Change is the law of life. And those who look only to the past or present are certain to miss the future." - John F. Kennedy</string>
        <string name="change_quote2">"Progress is impossible without change, and those who cannot change their minds cannot change anything." - George Bernard Shaw</string>
        <string name="change_quote3">"Change your thoughts and you change your world." - Norman Vincent Peale</string>
        <string name="change_quote4">"Change is inevitable. Growth is optional." - John C. Maxwell</string>
        <string name="change_quote5">"If you don't like something, change it. If you can't change it, change your attitude." - Maya Angelou</string>
        <string name="change_quote6">"The only way to make sense out of change is to plunge into it, move with it, and join the dance." - Alan Watts</string>
        <string name="change_quote7">"Change will not come if we wait for some other person or some other time. We are the ones we've been waiting for. We are the change that we seek." - Barack Obama</string>
        <string name="change_quote8">"The world as we have created it is a process of our thinking. It cannot be changed without changing our thinking." - Albert Einstein</string>
        <string name="change_quote9">"Change your life today. Don't gamble on the future, act now, without delay." - Simone de Beauvoir</string>
        <string name="change_quote10">"Change is painful, but nothing is as painful as staying stuck somewhere you don't belong." - Mandy Hale</string>
        <string name="change_quote11">"When we are no longer able to change a situation, we are challenged to change ourselves." - Viktor E. Frankl</string>
        <string name="change_quote12">"The art of life is a constant readjustment to our surroundings." - Kakuzo Okakura</string>
        <string name="change_quote13">"People don't resist change. They resist being changed!" - Peter Senge</string>
        <string name="change_quote14">"Change is hard at first, messy in the middle, and gorgeous at the end." - Robin Sharma</string>
        <string name="change_quote15">"Change is the end result of all true learning." - Leo Buscaglia</string>
        <string name="change_quote16">"Change, like sunshine, can be a friend or a foe, a blessing or a curse, a dawn or a dusk." - William Arthur Ward</string>
        <string name="change_quote17">"The only way to make a permanent change is to stop thinking about it and do something about it." - Karen Lamb</string>
        <string name="change_quote18">"You must be the change you wish to see in the world." - Mahatma Gandhi</string>
        <string name="change_quote19">"If you always do what you've always done, you'll always get what you've always got." - Henry Ford</string>
        <string name="change_quote20">"Change before you have to." - Jack Welch</string>
        <string name="change_quote21">"To improve is to change; to be perfect is to change often." - Winston Churchill</string>
        <string name="change_quote22">"They always say time changes things, but you actually have to change them yourself." - Andy Warhol</string>
        <string name="change_quote23">"Change your thoughts and you change your world." - Norman Vincent Peale</string>
        <string name="change_quote24">"Change is the constant, the signal for rebirth, the egg of the phoenix." - Christina Baldwin</string>
        <string name="change_quote25">"All great changes are preceded by chaos." - Deepak Chopra</string>
        <string name="change_quote26">"Change is not a threat, it's an opportunity. Survival is not the goal, transformative success is." - Seth Godin</string>
        <string name="change_quote27">"You can't stop the future. You can't rewind the past. The only way to learn the secret... is to press play." - Jay Asher</string>
        <string name="change_quote28">"Life belongs to the living, and he who lives must be prepared for changes." - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe</string>
        <string name="change_quote29">"Be the change that you wish to see in the world." - Mahatma Gandhi</string>
        <string name="change_quote30">"Change your life today. Don't gamble on the future, act now, without delay." - Simone de Beauvoir</string>
        <string name="change_quote31">"Change is inevitable. Growth is optional." - John C. Maxwell</string>
        <string name="change_quote32">"The only way to make sense out of change is to plunge into it, move with it, and join the dance." - Alan Watts</string>
        <string name="change_quote33">"Progress is impossible without change, and those who cannot change their minds cannot change anything." - George Bernard Shaw</string>
        <string name="change_quote34">"Change your thoughts and you change your world." - Norman Vincent Peale</string>
        <string name="change_quote35">"Change is the law of life. And those who look only to the past or present are certain to miss the future." - John F. Kennedy</string>
        <string name="change_quote36">"If you don't like something, change it. If you can't change it, change your attitude." - Maya Angelou</string>
        <string name="change_quote37">"Change will not come if we wait for some other person or some other time. We are the ones we've been waiting for. We are the change that we seek." - Barack Obama</string>
        <string name="change_quote38">"The world as we have created it is a process of our thinking. It cannot be changed without changing our thinking." - Albert Einstein</string>
        <string name="change_quote39">"Change is painful, but nothing is as painful as staying stuck somewhere you don't belong." - Mandy Hale</string>
        <string name="change_quote40">"When we are no longer able to change a situation, we are challenged to change ourselves." - Viktor E. Frankl</string>
    //FriendShip
        <string name="friendship_quote1">"Friendship is born at that moment when one person says to another: ‘What! You too? I thought I was the only one.’" - C.S. Lewis</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote2">"A real friend is one who walks in when the rest of the world walks out." - Walter Winchell</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote3">"Friendship is the only cement that will ever hold the world together." - Woodrow Wilson</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote4">"Friendship marks a life even more deeply than love. Love risks degenerating into obsession, friendship is never anything but sharing." - Elie Wiesel</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote5">"Friendship is the hardest thing in the world to explain. It's not something you learn in school. But if you haven't learned the meaning of friendship, you really haven't learned anything." - Muhammad Ali</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote6">"A friend is one that knows you as you are, understands where you have been, accepts what you have become, and still, gently allows you to grow." - William Shakespeare</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote7">"Friendship is the inexpressible comfort of feeling safe with a person, having neither to weigh thoughts nor measure words." - George Eliot</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote8">"A true friend is someone who thinks that you are a good egg even though he knows that you are slightly cracked." - Bernard Meltzer</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote9">"Friendship is born at that moment when one person says to another: ‘What! You too? I thought I was the only one.’" - C.S. Lewis</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote10">"A real friend is one who walks in when the rest of the world walks out." - Walter Winchell</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote11">"Friendship is the only cement that will ever hold the world together." - Woodrow Wilson</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote12">"Friendship marks a life even more deeply than love. Love risks degenerating into obsession, friendship is never anything but sharing." - Elie Wiesel</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote13">"Friendship is the hardest thing in the world to explain. It's not something you learn in school. But if you haven't learned the meaning of friendship, you really haven't learned anything." - Muhammad Ali</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote14">"A friend is one that knows you as you are, understands where you have been, accepts what you have become, and still, gently allows you to grow." - William Shakespeare</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote15">"Friendship is the inexpressible comfort of feeling safe with a person, having neither to weigh thoughts nor measure words." - George Eliot</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote16">"A true friend is someone who thinks that you are a good egg even though he knows that you are slightly cracked." - Bernard Meltzer</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote17">"Friendship is born at that moment when one person says to another: ‘What! You too? I thought I was the only one.’" - C.S. Lewis</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote18">"A real friend is one who walks in when the rest of the world walks out." - Walter Winchell</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote19">"Friendship is the only cement that will ever hold the world together." - Woodrow Wilson</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote20">"Friendship marks a life even more deeply than love. Love risks degenerating into obsession, friendship is never anything but sharing." - Elie Wiesel</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote21">"Friendship is the hardest thing in the world to explain. It's not something you learn in school. But if you haven't learned the meaning of friendship, you really haven't learned anything." - Muhammad Ali</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote22">"A friend is one that knows you as you are, understands where you have been, accepts what you have become, and still, gently allows you to grow." - William Shakespeare</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote23">"Friendship is the inexpressible comfort of feeling safe with a person, having neither to weigh thoughts nor measure words." - George Eliot</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote24">"A true friend is someone who thinks that you are a good egg even though he knows that you are slightly cracked." - Bernard Meltzer</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote25">"Friendship is born at that moment when one person says to another: ‘What! You too? I thought I was the only one.’" - C.S. Lewis</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote26">"A real friend is one who walks in when the rest of the world walks out." - Walter Winchell</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote27">"Friendship is the only cement that will ever hold the world together." - Woodrow Wilson</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote28">"Friendship marks a life even more deeply than love. Love risks degenerating into obsession, friendship is never anything but sharing." - Elie Wiesel</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote29">"Friendship is the hardest thing in the world to explain. It's not something you learn in school. But if you haven't learned the meaning of friendship, you really haven't learned anything." - Muhammad Ali</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote30">"A friend is one that knows you as you are, understands where you have been, accepts what you have become, and still, gently allows you to grow." - William Shakespeare</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote31">"Friendship is the inexpressible comfort of feeling safe with a person, having neither to weigh thoughts nor measure words." - George Eliot</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote32">"A true friend is someone who thinks that you are a good egg even though he knows that you are slightly cracked." - Bernard Meltzer</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote33">"Friendship is born at that moment when one person says to another: ‘What! You too? I thought I was the only one.’" - C.S. Lewis</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote34">"A real friend is one who walks in when the rest of the world walks out." - Walter Winchell</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote35">"Friendship is the only cement that will ever hold the world together." - Woodrow Wilson</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote36">"Friendship marks a life even more deeply than love. Love risks degenerating into obsession, friendship is never anything but sharing." - Elie Wiesel</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote37">"Friendship is the hardest thing in the world to explain. It's not something you learn in school. But if you haven't learned the meaning of friendship, you really haven't learned anything." - Muhammad Ali</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote38">"A friend is one that knows you as you are, understands where you have been, accepts what you have become, and still, gently allows you to grow." - William Shakespeare</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote39">"Friendship is the inexpressible comfort of feeling safe with a person, having neither to weigh thoughts nor measure words." - George Eliot</string>
        <string name="friendship_quote40">"A true friend is someone who thinks that you are a good egg even though he knows that you are slightly cracked." - Bernard Meltzer</string>
    //Courage
        <string name="courage_quote1">"Courage is resistance to fear, mastery of fear—not absence of fear." - Mark Twain</string>
        <string name="courage_quote2">"Courage is the most important of all the virtues because without courage, you can\'t practice any other virtue consistently." - Maya Angelou</string>
        <string name="courage_quote3">"Courage doesn\'t always roar. Sometimes courage is the little voice at the end of the day that says I\'ll try again tomorrow." - Mary Anne Radmacher</string>
        <string name="courage_quote4">"It takes courage to grow up and become who you really are." - E.E. Cummings</string>
        <string name="courage_quote5">"Courage is what it takes to stand up and speak; courage is also what it takes to sit down and listen." - Winston Churchill</string>
        <string name="courage_quote6">"You gain strength, courage, and confidence by every experience in which you really stop to look fear in the face." - Eleanor Roosevelt</string>
        <string name="courage_quote7">"Courage is not the absence of fear, but rather the assessment that something else is more important than fear." - Franklin D. Roosevelt</string>
        <string name="courage_quote8">"Success is not final, failure is not fatal: It is the courage to continue that counts." - Winston Churchill</string>
        <string name="courage_quote9">"Courage is grace under pressure." - Ernest Hemingway</string>
        <string name="courage_quote10">"The best way out is always through." - Robert Frost</string>
        <string name="courage_quote11">"Courage is being scared to death, but saddling up anyway." - John Wayne</string>
        <string name="courage_quote12">"Courage is resistance to domination, mastery of fear, not absence of fear." - Mahatma Gandhi</string>
        <string name="courage_quote13">"Success is not final, failure is not fatal: It is the courage to continue that counts." - Winston Churchill</string>
        <string name="courage_quote14">"Courage is knowing what not to fear." - Plato</string>
        <string name="courage_quote15">"Courage is the ladder on which all the other virtues mount." - Clare Booth Luce</string>
        <string name="courage_quote16">"Courage is the power to let go of the familiar." - Raymond Lindquist</string>
        <string name="courage_quote17">"Courage is the price that life exacts for granting peace." - Amelia Earhart</string>
        <string name="courage_quote18">"Life shrinks or expands in proportion to one\'s courage." - Anais Nin</string>
        <string name="courage_quote19">"Courage is not simply one of the virtues, but the form of every virtue at the testing point." - C. S. Lewis</string>
        <string name="courage_quote20">"To dare is to lose one\'s footing momentarily. To not dare is to lose oneself." - Soren Kierkegaard</string>
        <string name="courage_quote21">"Courage is the first of human qualities because it is the quality which guarantees the others." - Aristotle</string>
        <string name="courage_quote22">"Courage is the greatest of all virtues, because if you haven\'t courage, you may not have an opportunity to use any of the others." - Samuel Johnson</string>
        <string name="courage_quote23">"You can choose courage, or you can choose comfort, but you cannot choose both." - Brene Brown</string>
        <string name="courage_quote24">"Courage is the most important of all the virtues, because without courage you can\'t practice any other virtue consistently." - Maya Angelou</string>
        <string name="courage_quote25">"Courage is not the absence of fear, but rather the judgment that something else is more important than fear." - Ambrose Redmoon</string>
        <string name="courage_quote26">"It takes courage to grow up and become who you really are." - E.E. Cummings</string>
        <string name="courage_quote27">"The greatest test of courage on earth is to bear defeat without losing heart." - Robert Green Ingersoll</string>
        <string name="courage_quote28">"Courage, dear heart." - C.S. Lewis</string>
        <string name="courage_quote29">"Courage is what it takes to stand up and speak. Courage is also what it takes to sit down and listen." - Winston Churchill</string>
        <string name="courage_quote30">"Courage is not the absence of fear, but rather the assessment that something else is more important than fear." - Franklin D. Roosevelt</string>
        <string name="courage_quote31">"The secret of happiness is freedom, and the secret of freedom is courage." - Thucydides</string>
        <string name="courage_quote32">"Courage is not having the strength to go on; it is going on when you don\'t have the strength." - Theodore Roosevelt</string>
        <string name="courage_quote33">"Courage is not simply one of the virtues, but the form of every virtue at the testing point." - C.S. Lewis</string>
        <string name="courage_quote34">"Courage doesn\'t mean you don\'t get afraid. Courage means you don\'t let fear stop you." - Bethany Hamilton</string>
        <string name="courage_quote35">"Success is not final, failure is not fatal: It is the courage to continue that counts." - Winston Churchill</string>
        <string name="courage_quote36">"Courage is found in unlikely places." - J.R.R. Tolkien</string>
        <string name="courage_quote37">"It takes courage to grow up and become who you really are." - E.E. Cummings</string>
        <string name="courage_quote38">"Courage is not the absence of fear, but rather the judgment that something else is more important than fear." - Ambrose Redmoon</string>
        <string name="courage_quote39">"Courage is what it takes to stand up and speak. Courage is also what it takes to sit down and listen." - Winston Churchill</string>
        <string name="courage_quote40">"Courage is not the absence of fear, but rather the assessment that something else is more important than fear." - Franklin D. Roosevelt</string>
//Love
    <!-- Love Quotes -->

        <string name="love_quote1">"Love is composed of a single soul inhabiting two bodies." - Aristotle</string>
        <string name="love_quote2">"The best thing to hold onto in life is each other." - Audrey Hepburn</string>
        <string name="love_quote3">"You know you\'re in love when you can\'t fall asleep because reality is finally better than your dreams." - Dr. Seuss</string>
        <string name="love_quote4">"Love is like the wind, you can\'t see it but you can feel it." - Nicholas Sparks</string>
        <string name="love_quote5">"Being deeply loved by someone gives you strength, while loving someone deeply gives you courage." - Lao Tzu</string>
        <string name="love_quote6">"Love is when the other person\'s happiness is more important than your own." - H. Jackson Brown, Jr.</string>
        <string name="love_quote7">"In dreams and in love there are no impossibilities." - Janos Arnay</string>
        <string name="love_quote8">"Love isn\'t something you find. Love is something that finds you." - Loretta Young</string>
        <string name="love_quote9">"Love is the greatest refreshment in life." - Pablo Picasso</string>
        <string name="love_quote10">"The best and most beautiful things in this world cannot be seen or even heard, but must be felt with the heart." - Helen Keller</string>
        <string name="love_quote11">"Love is a friendship set to music." - Joseph Campbell</string>
        <string name="love_quote12">"To love and be loved is to feel the sun from both sides." - David Viscott</string>
        <string name="love_quote13">"Love is when you meet someone who tells you something new about yourself." - Andre Breton</string>
        <string name="love_quote14">"Love is of all passions the strongest, for it attacks simultaneously the head, the heart, and the senses." - Lao Tzu</string>
        <string name="love_quote15">"The best proof of love is trust." - Joyce Brothers</string>
        <string name="love_quote16">"The heart wants what it wants. There\'s no logic to these things. You meet someone and you fall in love and that\'s that." - Woody Allen</string>
        <string name="love_quote17">"Love is a game that two can play and both win." - Eva Gabor</string>
        <string name="love_quote18">"Love is when you sit beside someone doing nothing, yet you feel perfectly happy." - Unknown</string>
        <string name="love_quote19">"Love is like a butterfly. It goes where it pleases and it pleases wherever it goes." - Unknown</string>
        <string name="love_quote20">"The art of love is largely the art of persistence." - Albert Ellis</string>
        <string name="love_quote21">"Love is the only reality and it is not a mere sentiment. It is the ultimate truth that lies at the heart of creation." - Rabindranath Tagore</string>
        <string name="love_quote22">"Love is the flower you\'ve got to let grow." - John Lennon</string>
        <string name="love_quote23">"Love is the master key that opens the gates of happiness." - Oliver Wendell Holmes</string>
        <string name="love_quote24">"Love doesn\'t make the world go \'round. Love is what makes the ride worthwhile." - Franklin P. Jones</string>
        <string name="love_quote25">"Love is not finding someone to live with. It\'s finding someone you can\'t live without." - Rafael Ortiz</string>
        <string name="love_quote26">"Love is a canvas furnished by nature and embroidered by imagination." - Voltaire</string>
        <string name="love_quote27">"Love is an irresistible desire to be irresistibly desired." - Robert Frost</string>
        <string name="love_quote28">"Love is like war: easy to begin but very hard to stop." - H. L. Mencken</string>
        <string name="love_quote29">"Love is a better teacher than duty." - Albert Einstein</string>
        <string name="love_quote30">"Love is all we have, the only way that each can help the other." - Euripides</string>
        <string name="love_quote31">"The greatest happiness of life is the conviction that we are loved; loved for ourselves, or rather, loved in spite of ourselves." - Victor Hugo</string>
        <string name="love_quote32">"You know you\'re in love when you don\'t want to fall asleep because reality is finally better than your dreams." - Dr. Seuss</string>
        <string name="love_quote33">"Love is a game that two can play and both win." - Eva Gabor</string>
        <string name="love_quote34">"Love is when you sit beside someone doing nothing, yet you feel perfectly happy." - Unknown</string>
        <string name="love_quote35">"Love is like a butterfly. It goes where it pleases and it pleases wherever it goes." - Unknown</string>
        <string name="love_quote36">"The art of love is largely the art of persistence." - Albert Ellis</string>
        <string name="love_quote37">"Love is the only reality and it is not a mere sentiment. It is the ultimate truth that lies at the heart of creation." - Rabindranath Tagore</string>
        <string name="love_quote38">"Love is the flower you\'ve got to let grow." - John Lennon</string>
        <string name="love_quote39">"Love is the master key that opens the gates of happiness." - Oliver Wendell Holmes</string>
        <string name="love_quote40">"Love doesn\'t make the world go \'round. Love is what makes the ride worthwhile." - Franklin P. Jones</string>
   //Success

        <!-- Success Quotes -->

        <string name="success_quote1">Success is not final, failure is not fatal: It is the courage to continue that counts. - Winston Churchill</string>
        <string name="success_quote2">Success usually comes to those who are too busy to be looking for it. - Henry David Thoreau</string>
        <string name="success_quote3">The only place where success comes before work is in the dictionary. - Vidal Sassoon</string>
        <string name="success_quote4">Success is not how high you have climbed, but how you make a positive difference to the world. - Roy T. Bennett</string>
        <string name="success_quote5">Success is not the key to happiness. Happiness is the key to success. If you love what you are doing, you will be successful. - Albert Schweitzer</string>
        <string name="success_quote6">The only limit to our realization of tomorrow will be our doubts of today. - Franklin D. Roosevelt</string>
        <string name="success_quote7">Success is walking from failure to failure with no loss of enthusiasm. - Winston Churchill</string>
        <string name="success_quote8">Don’t be distracted by criticism. Remember, the only taste of success some people get is to take a bite out of you. - Zig Ziglar</string>
        <string name="success_quote9">Success is not measured by what you accomplish, but by the opposition you have encountered, and the courage with which you have maintained the struggle against overwhelming odds. - Orison Swett Marden</string>
        <string name="success_quote10">The road to success and the road to failure are almost exactly the same. - Colin R. Davis</string>
        <string name="success_quote11">Success is the sum of small efforts, repeated day in and day out. - Robert Collier</string>
        <string name="success_quote12">Success is not in what you have, but who you are. - Bo Bennett</string>
        <string name="success_quote13">Success is to be measured not so much by the position that one has reached in life as by the obstacles which he has overcome. - Booker T. Washington</string>
        <string name="success_quote14">Success is not just about making money; it’s about making a difference. - Unknown</string>
        <string name="success_quote15">The secret of success is to do the common thing uncommonly well. - John D. Rockefeller Jr.</string>
        <string name="success_quote16">Success seems to be connected with action. Successful people keep moving. They make mistakes, but they don’t quit. - Conrad Hilton</string>
        <string name="success_quote17">Success is not to be pursued; it is to be attracted by the person you become. - Jim Rohn</string>
        <string name="success_quote18">The only way to achieve the impossible is to believe it is possible. - Charles Kingsleigh</string>
        <string name="success_quote19">Success is not how far you got, but the distance you traveled from where you started. - Steve Prefontaine</string>
        <string name="success_quote20">Success is not final, failure is not fatal: It is the courage to continue that counts. - Winston Churchill</string>
        <string name="success_quote21">Success is not in what you have, but who you are. - Bo Bennett</string>
        <string name="success_quote22">The only place where success comes before work is in the dictionary. - Vidal Sassoon</string>
        <string name="success_quote23">Success is the sum of small efforts, repeated day in and day out. - Robert Collier</string>
        <string name="success_quote24">Success is not measured by what you accomplish, but by the opposition you have encountered, and the courage with which you have maintained the struggle against overwhelming odds. - Orison Swett Marden</string>
        <string name="success_quote25">Success is walking from failure to failure with no loss of enthusiasm. - Winston Churchill</string>
        <string name="success_quote26">Success is not just about making money; it’s about making a difference. - Unknown</string>
        <string name="success_quote27">The secret of success is to do the common thing uncommonly well. - John D. Rockefeller Jr.</string>
        <string name="success_quote28">Success is to be measured not so much by the position that one has reached in life as by the obstacles which he has overcome. - Booker T. Washington</string>
        <string name="success_quote29">Success seems to be connected with action. Successful people keep moving. They make mistakes, but they don’t quit. - Conrad Hilton</string>
        <string name="success_quote30">Success is not to be pursued; it is to be attracted by the person you become. - Jim Rohn</string>
        <string name="success_quote31">The only way to achieve the impossible is to believe it is possible. - Charles Kingsleigh</string>
        <string name="success_quote32">Success is not how far you got, but the distance you traveled from where you started. - Steve Prefontaine</string>
        <string name="success_quote33">Success is not final, failure is not fatal: It is the courage to continue that counts. - Winston Churchill</string>
        <string name="success_quote34">Success is not in what you have, but who you are. - Bo Bennett</string>
        <string name="success_quote35">The only place where success comes before work is in the dictionary. - Vidal Sassoon</string>
        <string name="success_quote36">Success is the sum of small efforts, repeated day in and day out. - Robert Collier</string>
        <string name="success_quote37">Success is not measured by what you accomplish, but by the opposition you have encountered, and the courage with which you have maintained the struggle against overwhelming odds. - Orison Swett Marden</string>
        <string name="success_quote38">Success is walking from failure to failure with no loss of enthusiasm. - Winston Churchill</string>
        <string name="success_quote39">Success is not just about making money; it’s about making a difference. - Unknown</string>
        <string name="success_quote40">The secret of success is to do the common thing uncommonly well. - John D. Rockefeller Jr.</string>
//grid
    <string name="change">change</string>
    <string name="friendship">friendship</string>
    <string name="courage">courage</string>
    <string name="love">love</string>
    <string name="success">success</string>
    <string name="wisdom">Wisdom</string>
    <string name="happiness">happiness</string>
    <string name="inspiring">inspiring</string>
    <string name="life">life</string>
    <string name="perseverance">perseverance</string>

</resources>